Mercury Press Records
Mercury Press Records
- Manuscripts (Part I)
  - London, Jack
    - The Angry Mammoth, May 1959; article (printed copy) (Box 27)
  - Lory, Robert
    - Mar-ti-an, April 1964; article (Box 27)
    - The Star Party, Sept. 1964; article (Box 27)
  - Lovecraft, H.P.
    - The Lamp of Alhazred, Oct., 1957; article (printed copy) (Box 27)
  - MacLean, Katherine
    - Interbalance, July 1961; article (Box 27)
  - MacLeish, Archibald
    - Epistle to Be Left in the Earth, Aug., 1963; poem (published in Collected Poems 1917-1952) (Box 27)
  - Malaval, Suzanne
    - The Devil's God-Daughter, Sept., 1962; article (translated by Damon Knight) (Box 27)
  - Mallette, Mose
    - The Seven Wonders of the Universe, Aug. 1966; article (Box 27)
  - Marner, Robert
    - A World Named Mary, May 1958; article (Box 27)
  - Marple, A.M.
    - Appoggiatura, April 1966; article (Box 27)
  - Marsh, Willard
    - Everyone's Home Town is Guernica, Aug., 1965; article (printed copy) (Box 27)
    - Forwarding Service, undated; article (printed copy) (Box 27)
    - Inconceivably Yours, Sept. 1964; article (Box 27)
    - Poet in Residence, May 1958; article (Box 27)
    - The Sin of Edna Schuster, Nov., 1965; article (Box 27)
  - Marshall, Audrey
    - Brain Bank, July 1966; article (Box 27)
  - Marti-Ibanez, Felix
    - Nina-Sol, May 1963; article (Box 27)
    - Senhor ZumBeirals Leg, Dec. 1962; article (Box 27)
  - Matheson, Richard
    - The Jazz Machine, Feb. 1963; article (Box 27)
    - Girl of My Dreams, Oct. 1963; article (Box 27)
    - The Edge, Aug. 1959; article (Box 27)
    - From Shadowed Places, Oct. 1960; article (Box 27)
    - The Holiday Man, July 1957; article (Box 27)
    - Lemmings, Aug. 1958; article (Box 27)
    - Old Haunts, March 1957; article (Box 27)
    - The Splendid Source, March 1957; article (Box 27)
    - Tis the Season To Be Jelly, June 1963; article (Box 27)
    - The Traveller, Feb., 1962; article (published in Born of Man and Woman) (Box 27)
  - McCaffrey, Anne
    - The Lady in the Tower, April 1959; article (Box 28)
    - The Ship Who Sang, April 1961; article (Box 28)
  - McClintic, Winona
    - Four Days in the Corner, June, 1961; article (Box 28)
    - The Way Out of Town, Aug. 1960; article (Box 28)
    - To Give Them Beauty For Ashes, Sept. 1959; poem (Box 28)
  - McIntosh, J.T.
    - Humanoid Sacrifice, Feb. 1962; article (Box 28)
    - One Into Two, March 1962; article (Box 28)
    - Poor Planet, Aug. 1964; article (Box 28)
    - The Sandmen, June 1957; article (Box 28)
    - The Stupid General, Aug. 1962; article (Box 28)
    - The Sudden Silence, Dec. 1966; article (Box 28)
    - Tenth Time Round, May 1959; article (Box 28)
  - McKenna, Richard
    - Casey, Sept. 1958; article (Box 28)
    - Mine Own Ways, Feb. 1960; article (Box 28)
    - Hunter, Come Home, March 1963; book (Box 28)
  - McLaughlin, Dean
    - The Voyage Which Is Ended, Aug. 1962; article (Box 28)
  - McMarrow, Fred
    - The Man From Tomorrow, May 1960; article (Box 28)
  - Merril, Judith
    - Theodore Sturgeon, 1962; article (Box 28)
    - Wish Upon A Star, Dec. 1958; article (Box 28)
    - Book reviews, 1965; 1966; 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Miller, P. Schuyler
    - For Analysis, Nov. 1958; article (Box 29)
  - Miller, Wade
    - How Lucky We Met, March 1960; article (Box 29)
  - Miller, Walter M. Jr.
    - The Last Canticle, Feb. 1957; article (Box 29)
    - Vengeance For Nikolai, March 1957; article (Box 29)
  - Miller, Wayne
    - I Know A Good Hand Trick, Oct. 1959; article (Box 29)
  - Mills, Robert
    - The Last Shall Be First, Aug. 1958; article (Box 29)
  - Mohler, Will
    - The Journey of Ten Thousand Miles, undated; article (Box 29)
  - Moore, Dick
    - After Everything, Nov. 1964; article (Box 29)
  - Moore, Hal R.
    - Sea Bright, Sept. 1965; article (Box 29)
  - Moore, Ward
    - Adjustment, May 1957; article (Box 29)
    - The Fellow Who Married The Maxill Girl, Feb. 1960; article (Box 29)
    - The Mysterious Milkman of Bishop Street, Dec., 1964; article (printed copy) (Box 29)
    - Rebel, undated; article (Box 29)
  - Morris, Wright
    - The Word From Space, Sept. 1958; article (Box 29)
  - Morrison, William
    - The Science Stage, 1957, March, May, June; 1958, March, May, June, July; articles (Box 29)
    - Stepping Stone, Dec. 1957; article (Box 29)
  - Morrissey, Doug
    - New Moon, Jan. 1958; article (Box 29)
  - Moskowitz, Sam
    - How Science Fiction Got Its Name,1957, Feb., article (Box 29)
    - Fantasy and Science Fiction by Theodore Sturgeon, 1962; bibliography (Box 29)
  - Murray, Robert
    - The Replacement, Feb. 1960; article (Box 29)
  - Nathan, Robert
    - A Pride of Carrots, Oct., 1959; play (Box 29)
  - Nelson, Ray
    - Eight O'Clock In The Morning, Nov. 1963; article (Box 29)
    - The Great Cosmic Donut of Life., undated; article (Box 29)
    - Turn Off The Sky, Aug. 1963; article (Box 29)
  - Nelson, Starr
    - For The Voyagers, Nov. 1958; poem (Box 29)
  - Nesradba, Josef
    - The Einstein Brain, May 1962; article (Box 30)
    - Pirate Island, undated; article (Box 30)
    - The Xeenemuende Half-Wit, May 1962; article (Box 30)
  - Neville, Kris
    - Closing Time, July 1961; article (Box 30)
  - Nayroud, Gerard E.
    - The Terra-Venusian War of 1979, Sept. 1959; article (Box 30)
  - Niven, Larry
    - Becalmed In Hell, July 1965; article (Box 30)
    - Bordered In Clack, April 1966; article (Box 30)
  - Nolan, William F.
    - Prose Poet in the Age of Space, May 1963; article (Box 30)
    - One of Those Days, May 1962; article (Box 30)
  - Novotny, John
    - The Biggest Damned Martini in the World, July 1958; article (Box 30)
    - The Meddler, Jan. 1958; article (Box 30)
    - Second Prize, Nov., 1957; article (Box 30)
    - A Trick or Two, July 1957; article (Box 30)
  - Oesterreicher, Arthur
    - Broken Circuit, April 1958; article (Box 30)
  - Olin, Richard
    - Lil Rorrity, and a Foamin' Sea of Steam Beer, undated; article (Box 30)
    - Oversight, Oct. 1964; article (Box 30)
  - Oliver, Chad
    - Didn't He Ramble, April 1957; article (Box 30)
    - The One That Got Away, May 1959; article (Box 30)
    - Pilgrimage, Feb., 1958; article (Box 30)
    - A Stick For Harry Eddington, Aug. 1965; article (Box 30)
    - Between the Thunder and the Sun, May 1957; book (Box 30)
    - End of the Line, Jan. 1964; book (Box 30)
    - Guardian Spirit, April 1950; book (Box 30)
    - The Wind Blows Free, undated; book (Box 30)
  - Ottum, Bob Jr.
    - Ado About Nothing, Jan. 1965; article (Box 30)
    - The Girls on Channel N, April 1957; article (Box 30)
  - Paine, J. Lincoln
    - The Dreistein Case, June 1958; article (Box 30)
  - Pangborn, Edgar
    - The Golden Horn, Oct. 1962; article (Box 30)
    - A War of No Consequence, article (Box 30)
    - Woggle Beast, Jan. 1964; article (Box 30)
    - Wrens in Grandpa's Whiskers, March 1960; article (Box 30)
    - The Red Hills of Summer, undated; book (Box 30)
  - Pederson, Con
    - Pushover Planet, 1963; article (Box 31)
  - Peterson, Nils
    - Cosmic Sex and You, June. 1960; article (Box 31)
    - Pecking Order, Sept., 1961 (Box 31)
    - Prelude to a Long Walk, Jan. 1962; article (Box 31)
  - Pettis, Nina
    - Witch's Charm, Sept. 1959; poem (Box 31)
  - Phillips, Rog
    - Executioner, Sept. 1957; article (Box 31)
    - Ground Leave Incident, May 1958; book (Box 31)
    - Love Me, Love My, Feb. 1958; article (Box 31)
    - Services, Incorporated, Jan. 1958; article (Box 31)
  - Piper, H. Beam
    - The Keeper, July 1957; article (Box 31)
  - Poe, Edgar Allen
    - A Tale of the Ragged Mountains, March 1958; article (Box 31)
  - Pohl, Frederik
    - Binary Digits and Human Habits, Dec. 1962; article (Box 31)
    - On C.M. Kornbluth, July 1958; article (Box 31)
    - Punch, 1963; article (Box 31)
    - To See Another Mountain, article (Box 31)
  - Pohl, Frederik, and C.M. Kornbluth
    - The World of Myrion Flowers, Oct. 1961; article (Box 31)
  - Porges, Arthur
    - The Mirror, Aug. 1966; article (Box 31)
    - Turning Point, undated; article (Box 31)
    - A Specimen for the Queen, May 1960; article (Box 31)
  - Posselt, Mildred
    - The Flower, poem (Box 31)
  - Pulley, James
    - The Space Twins, April 1966; article (Box 31)
  - Purdom, Tom
    - Green Place, Sept. 1964; article (Box 31)
  - Raffel, Burton
    - Goodbye, Aug. 1960; article (Box 31)
  - Raphael, Rick
    - Book reviews, undated (Box 31)
  - Reed, Kit
    - Automatic Tiger, Nov. 1964; article (Box 31)
    - Cynocure, June 1964; article (Box 31)
    - Devotion, June 1958; article (Box 31)
    - Empty Nest, April 1959; article (Box 31)
    - Judas Bomb, undated; article (Box 31)
    - The New You, 196A, article (Box 31)
    - On the Orphan's Colony, Dec. 1964; article (Box 31)
    - Piggy, Aug. 1911; article (Box 31)
    - The Reign of Tarquin the Tall, July 1958; article (Box 31)
    - Tell Me, Doctor -- Please, 1963; article (Box 31)
    - To Lift a Ship, Feb. 1962; article (Box 31)
    - Two in Homage, April 1960; article (Box 31)
    - The Wait, April 1958; article (Box 31)
  - Reeves, Rosser
    - Effigy, undated; poem (printed copy) (Box 31)
    - E=mc2, undated; poem (printed copy (Box 31)
    - Infinity, Dec., 1960; poems (Box 31)
  - Reis, Kathleen and R.H.
    - Ubi Sunt, undated; poem (Box 31)
  - Reynolds, Mack
    - Gladiator, March 1958; article (Box 31)
    - Snafu on the New Taos, Sept. 1957; article (Box 31)
    - Russkies Go Home, Nov. 1960; book (Box 31)
  - Rice, Jane
    - The Rainbow Gold, Dec. 1959; article (Box 32)
    - The White Pony, Feb. 1960; article (Box 32)
  - Richards, John Thomas
    - Minor Alteration, Aug. 1965; article (Box 32)
  - Robbins, Paul Jay
    - Sweets to the Sweets, 1963; article (Box 32)
  - Roberts, Jane
    - The Canvas Pyramid, March 1957; article (Box 32)
    - The Chest Beads, Oct. 1957; article (Box 32)
    - The Demon at Devotions, Sept. 1958; article (Box 32)
    - Impasse, Nov. 1959; article (Box 32)
    - Nightmare, April 1959; article (Box 32)
    - The Red Wagon, Nov. 1956; article (Box 32)
    - Three Times Around, May 1914; article (Box 32)
    - The Bundu, March 1958; book (Box 32)
  - Roberts, Keith
    - Survey of the Third Planet, Jan. 1966; article (Box 32)
  - Roberts, Mary-Carter
    - One Sent, Feb. 1958; article (Box 32)
    - When Jack Smith Fought Satan, July 1957; article (Box 32)
  - Rohrer, Robert
    - Explosion, July 1965; article (Box 32)
    - Keep Them Happy, April 1964; article (Box 32)
  - Rolf, Kenn
    - Satellite Trials, June 1959; article (Box 32)
  - Rose, Sharon
    - A Woman of the World, Jan. 1957; article (Box 32)
  - Rubin, Rick
    - The Interplanetary Cat, Sept. 1961; article (Box 32)
    - Final Muster, May 1961; article (Box 32)
  - Russ, Joanna
    - I Had Vacantly Crumpled It Into My Pocket...But, by God, Eliot, it was a Photograph from Life, July 1964; article (Box 32)
    - Mr. Wilde's Second Chance, Sept. 1966; article (Box 32)
    - My Dear Emily, July 1962; article (Box 32)
    - The New Men, Feb. 1966; article (Box 32)
    - Nor Custom Stale, Sept. 1959; article (Box 32)
    - There is Another Shore, You Know, Upon the Other Side, 1963; article (Box 32)
    - Wilderness Year, Nov. 1964; article (Box 32)
  - Russell, Maria
    - The Dear Park, Dec. 1962; article (Box 32)
  - Russell, Ray
    - The Rosebud, July 1959; article (Box 32)
  - St. Clair, Eric
    - Dimensional Analysis and Mr. Fortescue, Dec. 1964; article (Box 32)
    - Olsen and the Gulls, Sept. 1964; article (Box 32)
  - St. Clair, Margaret
    - Beaulieu, Nov. 1966; article (Box 32)
    - Gotterdammerung, Dec. 1956; article (Box 32)
  - Sanders, Winston P.
    - The Casuist, Sept. 1960; article (Box 32)
    - Pact, Aug. 1959; article (Box 32)
  - Sanford, Sue
    - Mrs. Pribley's Underdog, Feb. 1965; article (Box 33)
  - Scarff, William
    - The End of Winter, Jan. 1958; article (Box 33)
  - Schenck, Hilbert Jr.
    - Ed Lear Wasn't So Crazy, April 1961; poem (Box 33)
    - Me, June 1959; poem (Box 33)
    - Memo at the Department of Agriculture, April 1960; poem (Box 33)
    - Snip, Snip, June 1959; poem (Box 33)
    - Wockyjabber, April 1960; poem (Box 33)
  - Schmitz, James H.
    - These Are the Arts, 1962; article (Box 33)
  - Schutz, J.W.
    - Maiden Voyage, March 1965; article (Box 33)
  - Scott, Jody
    - The 2-D Problem, June 1965; article (Box 33)
  - Scott, Robin
    - The Gritsch System, May 1965; article (Box 33)
    - Near Thing, Aug. 1966; article (Box 33)
  - Seabright, Idris
    - The Death of Each Day, April 1958; article (Box 33)
    - Eithne, July 1957; article (Box 33)
  - Seabury, Paul
    - The Histronaut, 1963; article (Box 33)
  - Sellers, J.P.
    - Pete Gets His Man, 1963; article (Box 33)
  - Sharkey, Jack
    - Breakthrough, Oct. 1964; article (Box 33)
    - Collectors Item, 1963; article (Box 33)
    - Essentials Only, Feb. 1965; article (Box 33)
    - The Final Ingredient, June 1960; article (Box 33)
    - Survival of the Fittest, March 1964; article (Box 33)
    - Trade-In, July 1964; article (Box 33)
  - Sharon, Rose
    - The Lady Was A Tramp, March 1957; article (Box 33)
  - Shea, J. Vernon
    - H.P. Lovecraft: The House and the Shadows, May 1966; article (Box 33)
  - Silverberg, Robert
    - Eve and the Twenty-Three Adams, March 1958; article (Box 33)
    - The Man Who Never Forgot, Feb. 1958; article (Box 33)
    - The Nature of the Place, 1963; article (Box 33)
    - Warm Man, May 1957; article (Box 33)
    - The Winds of Siros, Sept. 1957; article (Box 33)
  - Sheckley, Robert
    - Dawn Invader, March 1957; article (Box 33)
    - The Girls and Nugent Miller, March 1960; article (Box 33)
    - Holdout, Dec. 1957; article (Box 33)
    - Love Incorporated - reprint, June 1957; article (Box 33)
    - The Prize of Peril, May 1958; article (Box 33)
    - The Journey of Jones, undated, Part II, Nov., 1962; book (Box 33)
  - Shepley, John
    - Gorilla Swift, May 1958; article (Box 34)
    - The Kit-Katt Klub, April 1962; article (Box 34)
    - Three for Carnival, May 1966; article (Box 34)
  - Shore, Wilma
    - A Bulletin from the Trustees of the Institute for Advanced Research at Marmouth, Mass., undated; article (Box 34)
  - Simak, Clifford D.
    - Shotgun Cure, Oct. 1961; article (Box 34)
    - All the Traps of Earth, March 1960; book (Box 34)
    - Final Gentleman, Jan. 1960; book (Box 34)
    - The Golden Bugs, June 1960; book (Box 34)
    - The Money Tree, July 1958; book (Box 34)
  - Simonds, Bruce
    - The Search, June 1964; article (Box 34)
  - Slesar, Henry
    - I Remember Oblivion, March 1966; article (Box 34)
    - Mating Season, July 1957; article (Box 34)
    - The Self-Improvement of Salvatore Ross, May 1961; article (Box 34)
    - Way-Station, 1963; article (Box 34)
  - Smith, Cordwainer
    - Alpha Ralpha Boulevard, June 1961; book (Box 34)
  - Smith, Evelyn E.
    - A Day in the Suburbs, Sept. 1960; article (Box 34)
    - Outcast of Mars, May 1957; article (Box 34)
    - Robert E. Lee at Moscow, Aug. 1961; article (Box 34)
    - Send Her Victorious, Feb. 1960; article (Box 34)
    - Softly While You're Sleeping, March 1961; article (Box 34)
    - They Also Serve, 1962; article (Box 34)
  - Smith, Hogan
    - The Year of the Earthman, Aug. 1964; article (Box 34)
  - Smith, Kenneth
    - With These Hands, 1963; article (Box 34)
  - Smith, Philip H. and Nourse, Alan E.
    - A Miracle Too Many, June 1964; article (Box 34)
  - Smith, Ron
    - The Horror Story Shorter Than The Shortest Ever Written, Feb. 1957; article (Box 34)
    - Tripsych, Dec. 1965; article (Box 34)
  - Smith, William J.
    - The Third Coordinate, Nov. 1964; article (Box 35)
  - Spinrad, Norman
    - The Age of Invention, June 1966; article (Box 35)
    - Neutral Ground, Nov. 1966; article (Box 35)
  - Stacey, J.C.
    - Know Your Elements, 1963; article (Box 35)
  - Stanton, Will
    - As Long As You Live, 1963; article (Box 35)
    - Dodger Fan, June 1957; article (Box 35)
    - The Gumdrop King, Aug. 1962; article (Box 35)
    - Over the River to What's-Her-Name's House, March 1958; article (Box 35)
    - The Scarecrow of Tomorrow, June 1962; article (Box 35)
    - Who Is Going to Cut the Barber's Hair?, Aug. 1959; article (Box 35)
    - You Are With It!, Dec. 1961; article (Box 35)
  - Steele, Wilbur Daniel
    - The Bogey Man, Nov. 1958; article (Box 35)
  - Stevens, Barry
    - Window to the Whirled, Feb. 1962; article (Box 35)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis
    - Something In It, Oct., 1966; article (submitted by Lawrence A. Perkins) (Box 35)
  - Stine, G. Harry
    - Sputnik: One Reason Why We Lost, Jan. 1958; article (Box 35)
    - The Truth of the Matter, Nov. 1956; article (Box 35)
  - Sturgeon, Theodore
    - Affair With A Green Monkey, May 1957; article (Box 35)
    - And Now the News, Dec. 1956; article (Box 35)
    - A Touch of Strange, Jan. 1958; article (Box 35)
    - The Comedian's Children, May 1958; article (Box 35)
    - The Girl Had Guts, Jan. 1957; article (Box 35)
    - It Opens the Sky, Nov. 1957; article (Box 35)
    - Like Young, March 1960; article (Box 35)
    - When You Care, When You Love, undated; article (Box 35)
  - Sturgis, Colin
    - The 24,000-Mile Field Goal, Jan. 1958; article (Box 35)
  - Suter, John F.
    - The Seeds of Murder, Aug. 1960; article, printed copy (Box 35)
  - Sutherland, Joan
    - The Struldbrugg Reaction, July 1964; article (Box 35)
  - Sutton, Lee
    - Soul Mate, June 1959; article (Box 35)
  - Swann, Burnett
    - The Manor of Roses, Nov. 1966; article (Box 35)
  - Sycamore, H.M.
    - Success Story, July 1959; article (Box 36)
  - Tabakow, Lou
    - The Day of the Millennium, May 1959; article (Box 36)
  - Tenn, William
    - Eastward Ho!, Oct. 1958; article (Box 36)
    - The Masculinist Revolt, Aug. 1965; book (Box 36)
  - Tevis, Walter
    - Far From Home, Nov. 1958; article (Box 36)
    - The Other End of the Line, Sept. 1961; article (Box 36)
  - Thomas, Gilbert
    - The Face is Familiar, Nov. 1966; article (Box 36)
    - Luana, July 1966; article (Box 36)
  - Thomas, Theodore, L.
    - The Building of a Protein, May 1964; article (Box 36)
    - The Science Springboard, 1961-1966; articles (Box 36)
      Carbonaceous Chondrites, Sept. 1964
      Desynchronosis, Feb. 1966
      Earth Tremor Detection, Nov. 1966
      The Intruder, Jan. 1961
      The Martian Atmosphere, Dec. 1966
      Medical Radio Tracers, June 1964
      Phoenix, June 1965
      Plant Galls, undated
      Pure Water from Salt, March 1964
      The Red Cells, Aug. 1964
      Smog, Jan. 1966
      Stomata, Oct. 1964
      Test, April 1962
  - Tilley, Robert J.
    - Apprentice, Dec. 1960; article (Box 36)
    - Place of Refuge, 1963; article (Box 36)
    - Something Else, Oct. 1965; article (Box 36)
  - Tomerlin, John
    - White Night, 1966; article (Box 36)
  - Tucker, Wilson
    - To the Tombaugh Station, July 1960; book (Box 36)
  - Turco, Lewis
    - A Great Grey Fantasy, April 1961; poem (Box 36)
    - Excerpts from the Latterday Chronicle, April 1962; article (Box 36)
  - Tushnet, Leonard
    - In the Calendar of Saints, May 1964; article (Box 36)
  - Twain, Mark
    - A Curious Pleasure Excursion, June 1961; article, copy (Box 36)
  - Updike, John
    - Cosmic Gall, Nov. 1961; poem (printed copy) (Box 36)
  - Vance, Jack
    - Green Magic, 1963; article (Box 36)
    - The Manse of Iucounu, undated; article (Box 36)
    - The Mountains of Magnatz, Feb. 1966; article (Box 36)
    - The Overworld, Dec. 1965; article (Box 36)
    - The Pilgrims, June 1966; article (Box 36)
    - The Sorcerer Pharesm, April 1966; article (Box 36)
  - Vandercook, John W.
    - Funk, Nov. 1960; article (Box 36)
  - Van Doren, Charles
    - SR, July 1957; article (Box 36)
  - Van Doren, Mark
    - The Little Place, June 1957; article (reprint) (Box 36)
    - The Witch of Ramoth, March 1958; article (reprint) (Box 36)
  - Van Scyoc, Sydney
    - One Man's Dream, undated; article (Box 37)
    - Zack With this Scar, undated; article (Box 37)
  - Vatsek, Joan
    - The Duel, May 1958; article (Box 37)
  - Veillot, Claude
    - The First Days of May, Dec. 1961; article (Box 37)
  - Verne, Jules
    - Frritt-Flocc, Oct., 1959; article (translated by I.O. Evans) (Box 37)
    - Gil Braltar, July, 1958; article (translated by I.O. Evans) (Box 37)
  - Vickers, Roy
    - The Eighth Lamp, July 1958; article (Box 37)
  - Vidal, Gore
    - Visit to a Small Planet, March 1957; play (duplicate proofs) (Box 37)
  - Vonnegut, Kurt, Jr.
    - Harrison Bergeron, Oct. 1961; article (Box 37)
  - Walker, Anne
    - The Oversight of Dirty-Jets Ryan, Dec. 1961; article (Box 37)
  - Wallace, F.L.
    - The Nevada Virus, undated; article (Box 37)
  - Wallace, Floyd
    - Privates All, Sept. 1961; article (Box 37)
  - Wallstein, Robert
    - Punk's Progress, 1963; article (Box 37)
  - Walpole, Horace
    - Saturnian Celia - extraction, Sept. 1957; article (Box 37)
  - Walton, Bryce
    - The Best is Yet to Come, Nov. 1966; article (Box 37)
    - Final Exam, June 1964; article (Box 37)
    - The Peace Watchers, April 1964; article (Box 37)
  - Watson, Billy
    - The Man Who Told Lies, Sept. 1959; article (Box 37)
  - Webb, Ron
    - The Girl With the 100 Proof Eyes, July 1964; article (Box 37)
  - Weller, Edward
    - Buffoon, Aug. 1964; article (Box 37)
    - Seven Days' Wonder, undated; article (Box 37)
  - Wellman, Manly Wade
    - Nine Yards of Other Cloth, Nov. 1958; article (Box 37)
    - Old Devlins Was A-Waiting, Feb. 1957; article (Box 37)
    - I Wonder As I Wander, March 1962; article (Box 37)
  - West, John Anthony
    - The Fiesta at Managuay, undated; article (Box 37)
    - George, June 1961; article (Box 37)
    - Gladys's Gregory, 1963; article (Box 37)
  - White, Don
    - Peter and Peggy Go to the Moon, 1963; article (Box 37)
    - Twenty-Four Hours in a Princess's Life With Frogs, Dec. 1962; article (Box 37)
    - Watch the Bug-Eyed Monster, May 1963; article (Box 37)
  - White, James
    - Christmas Treason, Jan. 1962; article (Box 38)
    - Counter Security, 1963; article (Box 38)
    - Fast Trip, 1963; article (Box 38)
  - White, Ted
    - The Peacock Trial, Aug. 1965; article (Box 38)
  - Whitehill, Joseph
    - Doctor Royker's Experiment, Sept. 1960; article (Box 38)
    - In the House, Another, April 1960; article (Box 38)
  - Wilde, Niall
    - A Divvil With the Women, Jan. 1960; article (Box 38)
  - Wilde, Oscar
    - Lord Arthur Savile's Crime, March 1964; article (Box 38)
  - Wilhelm, Kate
    - The Man Without a Planet, May 1962; article (Box 38)
    - A Time to Keep, Dec. 1962; article (Box 38)
  - Williams, Jay
    - The Beetle, March 1961; article (Box 38)
    - Gifts of the Gods, April 1962; article (Box 38)
    - Operation Ladybird, Aug. 1959; article (Box 38)
    - Somebody to Play With, March 1961; article (Box 38)
  - Williamson, Jack
    - Beans, Nov. 1958; article (Box 38)
  - Wilson, Richard
    - QRM, April 1957; article (Box 38)
    - The Venus Papers, Feb. 1958; article (Box 38)
  - Winkler, Richard
    - An Afternoon in May, Feb. 1962; article (Box 38)
  - Winsor, Phillip
    - Mama, 1963; article (Box 38)
    - Wodehouse, P.G.
    - Honeysuckle Cottage, Dec. 1958; article (printed copy) (Box 38)
  - Wolf, Leonard
    - Useful Knowledge, undated; poem (Box 38)
  - Wood, J.S.
    - Go For Baroque, Feb. 1961; article (Box 38)
  - Worthington, Will
    - Package Deal, June 1961; article (Box 38)
    - Plenitude, Nov. 1959; article (Box 38)
    - The Swamp Road, June 1960; article (Box 38)
    - We Are the Ceiling, Feb. 1960; article (Box 38)
    - Who Dreams of Ivy, Nov. 1960; article (Box 38)
  - Wyndham, John
    - Stitch in Time, March 1961; article (Box 38)
  - Young, Michael
    - The Time Keeper, Sept. 1961; article (Box 38)
  - Young, Robert F.
    - Added Inducement, March 1957; article (Box 38)